family How are you doing well I'm leaving
familia Qué tal estáis bueno os dejo
this so you can have breakfast okay I didn't
esto para que estéis desayunando vale no
want to tell you anything but I'm
os he querido decir nada pero estoy
taking a little trip related to
haciendo un viajecito relacionado con el
work okay I've been
trabajo okay llevo desde ayer por la
going crazy since yesterday morning I'll explain what's
mañana dando voltios ya os explicaré qué
going on what's happened and
es lo que pasa qué es lo que ha pasado y
where we are eh I'll tell you
por dónde andamos eh os lo comentaré
tomorrow probably or the day after okay I'll
mañana seguramente o pasado vale os lo
tell you tomorrow or the day after but
comentaré mañana o pasado pero
I'm doing a little job for you
estoy haciendo un trabajito para ustedes
okay the thing is that at one of
vale la movida es que en una en una de
these
estas
stops I was checking out
paradas me encontraba revisando ahora el
the comments a bit not from the
un poco los comentarios no de de los
latest videos and such that
últimos vídeos y demás que han estado
the Editors have been uploading during the afternoon and
subiendo los Editores durante la tarde y
I find that there was a comment
me encuentro con que había un comentario
from a lady who was asking me why I
de una señora que me decía que por qué
didn't talk about the trial that I lost and of
no hablaba del juicio que he perdido y
course I've gone crazy I've gone
claro me he vuelto loco me he vuelto
crazy trying to find out what trial I
loco para enterarme de qué juicio he
lost okay because it turns out I have the
perdido vale porque resulta que tengo a
whole gang of freaks
toda la pandillita de reventados
celebrating as if I had lost
celebrando como que yo había perdido
something okay so it took me a while to
algo vale entonces me ha costado
find out what it was but it
enterarme de qué es lo que era pero es
turns out that Diego Arrabal
que Resulta ser que Diego arrabal ha
uploaded a
subido un
video implying that I have been
vídeo dando a entender que me han
convicted that  has knocked down this mandate
condenado que me ha tumbado la manda
no
esta no
e If you watch the full live in reality
e Si ves el directo completo en realidad
Diego explains it more or less well although
Diego lo explica más o menos bien aunque
he lies and tells half-truths about
miente y dice verdades a medias en
many things but well Now we are going to
muchas cosas pero bueno Ahora la vamos a
clarify the good thing about this I would have
aclarar lo lo bueno que tiene esto Me
liked to do it in the studio
hubiera gustado hacerlo en el estudio
But the good thing about this is that everything
Pero lo bueno que tiene esto es que todo
is public so well there you can
está público entonces pues ahí lo podéis
check everything is worth But for the people and
comprobar todo vale Pero para la gente y
because he also makes it understood okay
porque él también la da a entender vale
for people like the lawsuit that I
para la gente como que la demanda que le
filed
puse
and that I have lost okay that they have
e que la he perdido vale que me han
sentenced me to Costa and that I have lost it
condenado a Costa y que la he perdido
okay the reality is that the lawsuit No,
vale la realidad es que no la demanda No
the trial has not started yet, it has not
no ha empezado todavía el juicio no ha
started, we do not even have a
empezado ni siquiera tenemos
response to the lawsuit nor do we have a
contestación a la demanda ni tenemos
preliminary hearing or the procedure
audiencia previa ni el procedimiento
yet it has not even started
todavía es que ni siquiera ha comenzado
okay this issue is very slow it is very
vale el tema este es muy lento da mucha
lazy I would have loved to
pereza a mí me hubiera encantado de
really I swear eh I say it
verdad os lo juro eh lo digo
sincerely to have fixed it in another
sinceramente haberlo arreglado de otro
way because it has been a long time I
modo porque ha pasado mucho tiempo Yo ya
am not even angry about this anymore I mean he
no estoy ni enfadado con esto O sea él
was like very uh angry like very
estaba como muy eh enfadado como muy
angry or something to me the truth is that it is
enojado o algo a mí la verdad es que es
something that does not take my life I do not care I would have
una cosa que no me quita la vida me da
liked  fix it But
igual me hubiera gustado arreglarla Pero
well it seems that it follows its course there is
bueno se ve que se ve que sigue su curso
no more when you are in a
no hay más cuando tú estás en un
procedure with someone Okay well the
procedimiento con alguien Vale pues las
parties during the procedure can
partes durante el procedimiento podéis
appeal and they can protest for several
recurrir y podéis protestar por varias
issues okay for example the other day
cuestiones vale por ejemplo el otro día
in a procedure in which I attended as a
en un procedimiento al que acudía yo de
witness not even I was a party
testigo ni siquiera yo era una parte
because the other party sent like a written
pues la otra parte mandó como un escrito
like an appeal I don't know what to call it no
como un recurso no sé cómo llamarlo no
because they didn't like that I was a
porque no le gustaba que yo fuera de
witness and they wanted to like cancel me as a
testigo y querían como cancelarme de
witness no and now there are times when they
testigo no y ya pues hay veces que te
accept an appeal or not okay in this
aceptan un recurso o no vale en este
case Diego who was within his right
caso Diego que estaba en todo su derecho
to do so and I imagined that he was going to
de hacerlo y yo me imaginaba que lo iba
do it okay and what he is appealing is not the
a hacer vale e lo que recurre no es la
lawsuit or in other words he has not yet
demanda o sea él todavía no ha
responded to the lawsuit he has not responded to
respondido a la demanda no ha contestado
the lawsuit he is not appealing the lawsuit
la demanda él no recurre la demanda él
what he has done is to
lo que ha hecho es
appeal
e recurrir
so that you understand me so as not to
el para que me entendáis para no
get into legal terms okay the
meternos en términos jurídicos vale el
appropriate court the competent court
juzgado procedente el juzgado competente
to carry out this procedure
para llevar este procedimiento
Okay my lawyer presented it in A Coruña
Vale mi abogado lo presentó en la Coruña
because we have a criminal matter
porque nosotros tenemos un tema penal
that you all know about for many
que todos conocéis de hace muchísimos
years okay for which I do not want to give my
años vale por el que yo no quiero dar mi
address okay for me and Pablo
dirección vale yo para mí y Pablo
too  I saw it as justified for me It
también lo veía justificado para mí
was completely justified not to
Estaba completamente justificado no
tell this person where I live in the
decirle a esta persona dónde vivo en
first place because this person, as
primer lugar porque est persona como ya
you all know, had already published my license plate, the first thing he did when he received this procedure was to start releasing content about everything, absolutely everything, he even made an appeal to all the defendants to give him information. Also, when I was on vacation at the beach, I was publishing
vacaciones en la playa he ido publicando
stories about which beach I was at.
histori de qué playa yo me encontraba
So how can you understand with what
Entonces cómo comprenderéis con lo que
I have on my back, I
yo tengo encima pues no me agrada la
really don't like having to give my address. Okay, does
verdad tener que dar mi dirección Okay
this mean that we file
esto quiere decir que nosotros pongamos
the lawsuits in Galicia because we like
las demandas en Galicia porque nos gusta
octopus or because it's cheaper for me, how do I
el pulpo o porque me sale más barato
understand? No. Or it's free for me as a
como ad entender no O me sale gratis de
buddy. No. When we filed a
coleguilla no no cuando le pusimos una
complaint against a friend
denuncia al amigo
of a YouTuber in Malaga, not against
de un youtuber en Málaga no al amigo de
my friend Juan, it was there, I don't know if it was strong, I do
yo Juan se puso allí no sé si era fuerte
n't know if it was Benalmadena, I don't remember
no sé si era benalmadena no me acuerdo
where it was and it was done there, we won without a problem.
dónde fue y se hizo allí sin problema la
Okay, when we filed the
ganamos Vale cuando le pusimos la
complaint against the stalker, no, eh. The stalker
denuncia al acosador no eh Al acosador
that I have, no. He's doing it in
que tengo no Esto está haciendo en
Seville, then he found out that the guy was
Sevilla después averiguó que el tipo era
G and he's still playing in Seville  No one has
G y se sigue jugando en Sevilla nadie ha
protested and the game continues to be played in Seville.
protestado y se sigue jugando en Sevilla
Eh, there is another lawsuit that we have filed, we have
Eh hay otra demanda que tenemos puesta
several plaintiffs,
que la tenemos puesta varios demandantes
each one from a different city, each one at one
cada uno de una ciudad cada uno en una
end, okay, if the defendant wants, if
punta vale si quiere la demandada si se
the procedure is filed because of course it
presenta el procedimiento porque claro
would be interesting if it were filed if
sería interesante que se presentase si
the defendant wants. Well, let it be discussed.
quiere la demandada Pues que se discuta
In which city, no. In which four cities
En qué ciudad no En qué cuatro ciudades
can it be done, okay, that would also be an
se pueden hacer vale también sería una
option, eh,
opción eh
and like this, I can give a lot of
y como esto puedo poner un montón de
examples, okay. He is within his right to
ejemplo okay Él está en todo su derecho
not like Galicia, to like
de que no le guste Galicia le guste más
Seville more, and that he wants it to be done in
Sevilla y que quiere que se haga en
Seville. Personally, Diego, and I
Sevilla yo personalmente Diego y te lo
tell you this with all due respect and from the heart,
digo con todo el respeto y de corazón yo
personally, what I would have liked
personalmente lo que me hubiese gustado
is,
es
eh, that you had contacted me and that we
eh que me hubieras contactado y que
had talked and that I could have taken it away from you, okay.
hubiéramos hablado y que te la quite
And I tell you this completely sincerely
vale Y te lo digo completamente sincero
because I am not making
porque es que tampoco te estoy poniendo
things difficult for you, nor am I
las cosas difíciles tampoco te estoy
fooling you, nor am I bragging about it, it's been a
vacilando ni te estoy chuleando que hace
long time, honestly, these
mucho tiempo es que sinceramente estas
things make me very lazy, I
cosas a mí me da mucha pereza a mí me
would have loved not to have to come to
hubiera encantado no tener que llegar a
this, but what you're saying
esto pero es que lo que estás diciendo
is not true, it's not true, it's
no es verdad es que no es verdad es que
saying that the content of the
está diciendo que el contenido de la
lawsuit is a lie, the content of  the
demanda es mentira el contenido de la
lawsuit is not a lie the content of the
demanda no es mentira el contenido de la
lawsuit is not that you put a picture
demanda no es que tú te pongas una foto
on your forehead okay the content of the
en la frente vale el contenido de la
lawsuit is a series of live broadcasts and a
demanda son una serie de directos y una
series of insults that you in your live broadcast
serie de insultos que tú en tu directo
today you have returned so it is a lie and it
hoy has vuelto así que es mentira y no
is not a lie I mean it is not a lie you were in
es mentira o sea no es mentira estuviste
a few live broadcasts telling me eh
unos cuantos de directos diciéndome eh
sewer rat that I am not a man that
rata de cloaca que no soy un hombre que
I took advantage of Marta and the
me aproveché de Marta y de la de la
problem that Marta had and that if my
problema que tenía Marta e que si mis
tattoos that if my rings that if I
tatuajes que si mis anillos que si me
hit you from behind I don't know what you were
pego por detrás no sé que estabas
insinuating there a bunch of insults
insinuando ahí un montón de insultos
Diego that I have not done to you what
Diego que yo a ti no te he hecho que me
have you told me Ah no I do not ask you for forgiveness
has dicho Ah no Yo no te pido perdón
because what you have done to the Channel
porque lo que tú le has hecho al Canal
What have I done to you I mean what I criticized you
Qué te he hecho O sea qué te critiqué
with the Pantoja car dude
con lo del coche de la Pantoja tío
you want me to remove it I will remove it just like you
quieres que quite el yo lo quito igual
contacted me to remove a
que me contactaste para que quitara una
min dude because it was a photo that you had
min tío porque era una foto que habías
taken you ask me dude I will remove it
hecho tú pídemelo tío yo lo quito yo
for me at that moment it was a
para mí en ese momento era una crítica
valid criticism the other day Kiko Hernández
válida el otro día Kiko Hernández te
told you that  they had stopped you in Malaga or
dijo que te habían detenido en Málaga o
in Marbella that they had stopped you with
en Marbella que te habían detenido con
the car and you didn't tell him the same thing You
el coche y no le dijiste lo mismo A mí
've insulted me, you've been
me has insultado me has estado haciendo
insulting me in a lot of live streams that
insultos en un montón de directos que
are there presented, one of the live
están ahí presentados uno de los
streams you have in private on your
directos los tienes en privado en tu
secondary channel that we have
canal secundario que lo tenemos
downloaded obviously and it's
descargado evidentemente y está
presented, the lawsuit that
presentado no es mentira la demanda que
you think is [ __ ] is not a lie. Well,
a ti te parece que son chorradas Bueno
hey, look, I consider that they are
oye Mira yo Considero que son
disproportionate for the treatment that I have
desproporcionados para el trato que te
given you. It's not that I knew you from the
he dado yo no es que yo te calé desde el
first moment, it's not true either Diego, it
primer momento tampoco es verdad Diego
's not true either. You have been
tampoco es verdad tú has estado
collaborating with me, eh, I have on my
colaborando conmigo eh tengo en mi
Instagram account that I have uploaded, I have
cuenta de Instagram que lo tengo subido
n't deleted it, a video in which they
no lo he borrado un vídeo en el que
say what a good person I am, what a good
dicen lo buena gente que soy lo buen
partner I was when I
compañero que fui cuando me ofrecí para
offered to help you for the entire platform, that's it, for whatever reason you decided or suddenly you didn't like me, you are within your rights, but I have not, I have not insulted you or disrespected you ever in the first place, okay, in the first place because the
vale en primer lugar porque en el
moment I saw that you were serious, that you
momento que vi que estabas en serio que
were angry, I already tried to avoid
estabas picado yo ya intenté esquivar a
talking about you, dude, I mean  when you
hablar de ti tío o sea cuando tú más
're most taking out my C of mine from the year of the
estás sacando a mí C mío del año de la
pig insulting I don't know who that you don't even
porca insultando no sé quién que ni
know who you're insulting or
sabes a quién estás insultando ni el por
why I haven't started saying that you
qué yo no me he puesto a decir que tú
insult women I haven't started
insultas a las mujeres no me he puesto a
showing you videos of María Patiño on all
sacarte vídeos de María Patiño a cuatro
fours this that other no I haven't started
patas esto lo otro no me no me he puesto
taking you old clicks I haven't started
a sacarte clicks antiguo no me he puesto
showing you this live that they
a sacarte el directo este que que se
mess with you for a live that you did that
meten contigo por un directo que hiciste
is deleted also not in a position to
que está borrado también no puesto a
tell you anything dude I mean absolutely
decirte nada tío o sea absolutamente
nothing you told me in the video in the
nada me me has dicho en el vídeo en el
live of Now that I am very well known in
directo de Ahora que soy muy conocido en
the Barcelona court dude seriously
el jugado de Barcelona tío en serio en
seriously dude you no you are not known
serio tío tú no tú no eres conocido por
there anyway eh it is completely
allí en fin eh es completamente
disproportionate dude obviously Of course
desproporcionado tío evidentemente Claro
I would have liked to fix it in
que me hubiera gustado arreglarlo de
another way but I had no other choice because you did
otra forma pero no me quedó otra porque
n't stop and there are a
es que no parabas y hay un hay unos
few live shows and there are a few
cuantos de directos y hay unos cuantos
videos that will still be presented at
de vídeos que todavía se presentarán en
the preliminary hearing if we arrive no
la audiencia previa si llegamos no
because I see that it looks like they were
porque veo que tiene toda la pinta que
not submitted to the lawsuit there are even
no se aportaron a la demanda hay todavía
more videos where you said more
más vídeos donde dijiste más
barbarities for me  violating my honor
barbaridades para mí vulnerando mi honor
dude It's not that he criticized me because I was driving while
tío No es que me criticó porque iba con
recording La Pantoja Well it's not
el coche grabando la Pantoja Bueno no es
that he told me I don't remember what But
que me dijo No me acuerdo el qué Pero lo
what I do remember perfectly
que sí que me acuerdo perfectamente
Diego arrabal and I say this with all the
Diego arrabal y te lo digo con todo el
respect in the
respeto del mundo tío y te lo estoy
world dude and I'm saying this to you because of your age, because of the professional that you are and because we're simply not connected Well I'm not disrespecting you dude I'm saying this with all the respect in the world I'm sangel tema with a super chat in your live that's
con un super chat en tu directo que está
there And it's also presented in the lawsuit
ahí Y está presentado en la demanda
each one on their own Diego for
también cada uno por su lado Diego por
my part [ __ ] great for whatever you
mi parte de madre para lo que
want I don't know what I don't know what I put but I
quiera no sé qué no sé lo que puse pero
sent you a super chat I put it in a
te mandé un super chat lo puse en
statement on my YouTube community tab
comunicado en mi pestaña comunidad de
and I put it in my tweet and there it is, I have
YouTube y lo puse en mi tweet y ahí está
n't deleted it if what it has
no lo he borrado si es que lo que tiene
what I'm saying is that it's
lo que estoy contando es que está
public anyone can check it And
público lo puede comprobar cualquiera Y
your insults are real dude your insults
tus insultos son reales tío tus insultos
are real Well I don't see that it's
son reales Pues yo no veo que sea una
[ __ ] or that a lawsuit
chorrada o que no tenga peso una demanda
in which you call me a dirty rat
en la que tú me llamas rata sucia rata
sewer rat has no weight  you're behind I don't know a
de cloaca que vas por detrás no sé un
lot of insults so many you have put in
montón de insultos tantos hais puesto en
the complaint and other videos that will be
la demanda y otros vídeos que se
provided at the preliminary hearing that
aportarán en la audiencia previa que que
I have not told you those things man I mean
yo no te he dicho esas cosas tío O sea
I have not told them to you and it's that I
que yo no te las he dicho y es que
sincerely believe that I can't do more I mean
sinceramente creo que no puedo hacer más
what have I told you to delete the
O sea e qué te he dicho que borres los
videos that is damaging to your game
vídeos eso te supone un daño a tu juego
and it doesn't mean anything to me if you ask me to
e a mí no me supone nada si tú me pides
delete a video I mean the
que borre un vídeo o sea es que la
truth is that that is what is causing you
verdad es que eso es lo que te supone un
great damage that you want us to take it
gran daño que tú quieres que lo llevemos
to the end we take it to the
hasta el final lo llevamos hasta el
end we take it to the end I don't know
final lo llevamos hasta el final no sé
at what point you thought it was a good idea
en qué momento te ha parecido buena idea
a live selling like you won
un directo vendiendo como que has ganado
like congratulations to my lawyers I don't know
como felicidades a mis abogados no sé
what Look
qué Mira
and if my lawyer was wrong in the
e si mi abogad se ha equivocado en la
competition and if not well he was
competencia y si no te bueno se ha
wrong or he considered that there was
equivocado o él consideraba que había
more than enough reason to
motivo más que suficiente para
present it there okay
presentarla allí vale
when you appeal and say No, it's that they haven't
cuando tú recurres y dices No es que no
responded to the appeal Why not
han respondido al recurso Por qué no por
why don't you respond to the appeal Well because
qué no respondes al recurso Pues porque
we don't oppose it I mean why am I going to
no nos oponemos o sea para qué te voy a
respond to an appeal that we do not
responder a un recurso que no nos
oppose  what do you want in Seville Well in
oponemos qué quieres en Sevilla Pues en
Seville we do it we don't oppose okay
Sevilla lo hacemos no nos oponemos vale
my lawyer has made
que mi abogado ha tenido comentarios
unfortunate comments for you Diego totally
desafortunados para ti Diego totalmente
dude you deal with him you sue
tío te las apañes con él lo demandas a
him and it's between you two dude I haven't
él y es cosa entre ustedes dos tío yo no
told you when Franco is here he
te las he dicho cuando Franco está
messed with you because of what you found out that
se metió contigo por lo que sacaste que
Daniel Sancho wasn't the one from the
Daniel Sancho no era el de las cámaras
security cameras or Mika Vasco also
de seguridad o Mika Vasco también se
messed with you I don't know if it's for the same reason you
metió contigo no sé si por lo mismo te
started messing with me dude you
empezaste a meter conmigo tío te
started messing with me to my face and
empezaste a meter conmigo por la cara y
there it is it's public you
ahí está es que está público te
started messing with me blaming
empezaste a meter conmigo culpándome a
me for what they were telling you I
mí de lo que te estaban diciendo ellos
don't have a friendship with Mik It's been a
yo con mik no tengo una amistad Hace
long time since we spoke okay at that
mucho tiempo que no hablamos vale en ese
time well we had the same thing now
momento pues teníamos la misma c ahora
a cordiality but we don't have a
una cordialidad pero tampoco tenemos una
friendship either whatever she told you she would
amistad ella lo que te dijera te lo
tell you on her own as for Fran I am
diría por su cuenta a Fran tengo
absolutely forbidden that when she's with me she
prohibidísimo que cuando esté conmigo se
starts mentioning you or getting into
ponga a mencionarte o a entrarte al
it when you provoke her or anything like that
trapo cuando tú lo picas ni nada por el
dude or whatever you have with
estilo tío o sea lo que tengas tú con
Fran you deal with Fran or I mean what I
Fran te las apañes con Fran o sea yo lo
know is that I  bury the
que sé es que yo enterre el hacha de
hatchet I still have the statements
guerra yo tengo los comunicados todavía
public okay And I have received a series
públicos vale Y yo he recibido una serie
of violations that I think are
de vulneraciones que yo creo que son
disproportionate that you say are
desproporcionadas que tú dices que son
lies and that I have to prove them Well
mentiras y que las tengo que demostrar
yes, there are the videos but if it's that you
Pues si estás los vídeos pero si es que
also mention me by name and
además me mencionas con nombre y
surname in the videos in which you
apellido en los vídeos en los que me
are
estás insultando
constantly insulting me and in some of them you
constantemente y en algunos de ellos
even ask for calls to your
incluso pides llamadas a tu
number that you have to pay to call you on that
número que hay que pagar para llamarte
phone number you didn't have to pay for I don't know
al teléfono ese no había que pagar No sé
if you still have it to heat up the
si lo tienes todavía para caldear el
atmosphere and have people talk about my
ambiente y que la gente hablara de mí
uncle, I mean, for me it's disproportionate that
tío o sea para mí desproporcionado que
you think is proportionate Well nothing
tú crees que es proporcionado Pues nada
Son, we'll be suing for a few years,
Hijo nos pegaremos unos años
I personally see it and I
pleiteando yo personalmente lo veo y te
tell you with all due respect Diego, I
lo digo con todo el respeto e Diego o
mean, the truth is I was happy when things have
sea de verdad me he alegrado cuando te
gone well for you on YouTube ok you said that
ha ido bien en YouTube ok has dicho que
for me it's just that things are going well The
a mí nada más que me va bien Los
conflicts and that I'm doing this
conflictos y que esto lo estoy haciendo
to monetize I haven't taken out content from this I
para monetizar yo de esto no sacado
think the live shows you've
contenido creo que los directos que has
done talking about this topic have been
hecho hablando sobre este tema han sido
among the ones with the most viewers and
de los que más espectadores has tenido e
you're the one who took out  the live issue
eres tú el que has sacado el tema en
I have not said anything okay And
directo yo no he contado nada vale Y
you are the one who has made videos about
eres tú el que has sacado vídeos sobre
this subject I have responded
este tema yo he respondido
okay that I have gone or that Marina has
vale que yo he ido o que Marina me ha
done me a favor So that they take out
hecho un favor Para que saquen en la
the article in reason that I also
razón el artículo que eso también lo
heard that a lot of times Marina was on sick
escuchó un montón de veces Marina estaba
leave at that time and apart from that
de baja en aquel momento y aparte ese
article it does not benefit me that
artículo no me beneficia a mí ese
article tells your version because you
artículo cuenta tu versión porque tú
did a live if they had
hiciste un directo si a mí me hubieran
asked me I would have said more or
preguntado yo hubiera dicho pues más o
less what I am saying here now
menos lo que estoy diciendo aquí ahora
the insults that you made to me so that I
los insultos que me hiciste para que yo
sue you and then that you have continued
te demandas y luego que has continuado
that there is a is that there are a lot of
que hay un es que hay un montón de
insults and there are a lot of videos that
insultos y hay un montón de vídeos que
are not presented yet okay or that is that in
no están presentado todavía vale o sea
that article Marina does me
que que ese artículo Marina me hace a mí
the favor and that now they have to
el favor y que ahora lo tienen que
rectify it if you considered that they
rectificar si tú considerabas que lo
had to rectify it Diego You know
tenían que rectificar Diego Tú sabes
perfectly well that you have seven days to do it
perfectamente que tienes siete días para
and that you have not done it and if
hacerlo y que no lo has hecho y si
tomorrow they publish an article saying that I
mañana sacan un artículo diciendo que yo
have lied to justice Well I am going to
le he mentido a la justicia Pues le voy
send her the right to rectification
a mandar yo el derecho a rectificación
okay And that's it dude without more I mean I
vale Y ya está tío sin más O sea yo más
can't do more Diego dude or I mean I ca
no puedo hacer Diego tío o sea yo más
n't make it easier  I wish the people who
fácil no lo puedo poner Ojalá la gente
have sued me I wish the people
que me ha demandado a mí Ojalá la gente
who have sued me had
que me ha demandado a mí me lo hubiera
made it as simple as sorry eh I delete
puesto tan sencillo como perdón eh borro
the videos and each one has his life, each one has
los vídeos y cada uno su vida cada uno
his job because as you have said
su trabajo que como tú bien has dicho la
life goes on and life must be
vida va pasando y la vida hay que
lived if you don't want to I can't I
vivirla si no quieres yo no puedo yo no
can't do anything else I can't close
puedo hacer otra cosa yo no puedo cerrar
the procedure yes if you don't want to
el procedimiento si si tú no quieres
reach an agreement or that we talk or that or or
llegar a un acuerdo o que hablemos o que
remove the videos I mean it's because you don't
o o quitar los vídeos o sea es que no
want anything then I can't do anything other
quieres nada entonces yo no puedo hacer
than continue with the
otra cosa que seguir con el
procedure man and the
procedimiento tío y es completamente
way you have sold it is completely false
falso la forma en la que la has vendido
as if I had lost the
como si yo hubiera perdido el
procedure
procedimiento
like I mean if what you just
como o sea si es que lo que acabas de
won is an appeal that we have not
ganar es un recurso al que nosotros no
opposed Diego I do not oppose
nos hemos opuesto Diego yo no me opongo
man I do not oppose I only
tío yo no me opongo Yo lo único que hago
try and find solutions that you
es intentar y poner soluciones que tú
want then nothing I consider that my
quieres pues nada yo Considero que está
honor has been violated, I mean you laughed
vulnerados el honor o sea te has reído
no and you have emphasized the lawsuits
no y has hecho hincapié de las demandas
that I have lost Look at the expressions
que yo he perdido Mira las expresiones
of the lawsuits that I have lost
de las demandas que yo he perdido
Diego they are not inferior to the ones I am
Diego no son inferiores a las que yo te
suing you for  that you want us to
demando a ti que tú quieres que
go all the way I see it as
lleguemos hasta el final lo veo
completely unnecessary because
completamente innecesario porque yo lo
all I want is an apology for it to be
único que quiero es una disculpa que se
withdrawn Hey you want me to withdraw
retire Oye que tú quieres que yo retire
something too no problem dude I don't
algo también sin problema tío yo no
have the LEGO super flag and this is not taking my
tengo el LEGO super flag ni esto me me
life away I really tell you from the
quita la vida de verdad te lo digo de
heart eh and then out of the way dude I
corazón eh y ya luego fuera parte tío O
mean the gang of freaks with what they
sea la pandilla de reventados con lo que
saw this week this has nothing to do with it
ha vio esta semana ya esto no tiene nada
Diego nor Diego will know what's
que ver Diego ni Diego sabrá de lo que
going on with what they saw this week
va la cosa con lo que ha vio esta semana
that you're celebrating that I'm
que estéis celebrando que estoy
celebrating that they won an appeal
celebrando que me ganen un recurso de
where the trial is held if in Andalusia
dónde se hace el juicio si en Andalucía
or in Galicia to which I have not opposed
o en Galicia al que yo no me he opuesto
the truth is that you're giving me a lot of
la verdad es que me estáis dando mucha
[ __ ] okay the one from Troy saying The
cosilla vale al de Troya diciendo El
karma The karma what the one from Troy who have
karma El karma qué al de Troya a quién
I won an appeal against or with whom have I
le he ganado yo un recurso o con quién
argued about where
he discutido yo de dónde hay que hacer
a trial should be held you know what the
un juicio sabes lo que significa la
word karma means dude I mean what what what what
palabra karma tío O sea qué qué qué qué
Really or rather a few days ago I had to
De verdad o sea Hace unos días tuve que
deny a few days ago I had to
desmentir hace unos días tuve que
deny because they were opening
desmentir porque estaban abriendo
live and they were celebrating that YouTube
directo y estaban celebrando que YouTube
had taken action against me that
había tomado medidas contra mí que
YouTube had taken action against me
YouTube había tomado medidas contra mí
that YouTube was getting serious that there
que YouTube se estaba poniendo serio que
was YouTube at the time that it has
había YouTube en el momento que lo ha
appealed has said this that it was
apelado ha dicho esto que qu fuera
also No neither n more the ridiculous
también No tampoco n más el ridículo
Okay
Vale
and and a little more a little more family eh I will
y y poco más poco más familia eh yo os
tell you Soon what has
contaré Dentro de poco qué es lo que ha
happened where we are And what is it that
pasado por dónde andamos Y qué es lo que
And what is it that I have to Show you
Y qué es lo que os tengo que Mostrar
okay let's see how it turns out let's see how it turns out I will
vale a ver cómo sale a ver cómo sale
probably finish today and And
terminaré probablemente hoy y Y
surely later later we will talk okay what I
seguramente luego luego hablemos vale lo
said eh a kiss I hope I haven't
dicho eh un beso Espero no haberme
left anything out I think I haven't left
dejado nada Creo que no me he dejado
anything out Okay I'm speaking from memory
nada Okay os estoy hablando de memoria
I would have liked to answer this more
me hubiera gustado más contestar a esto
I would have liked not to have to
Me hubiera gustado no tener que
answer this the truth I mean I would have
contestar a esto la verdad O sea me
liked to do things
hubiera gustado hacer las cosas
well with
bien con
maturity but well
madurez pero bueno en
anyway we continue a kiss
fin continuamos un beso